[ Watch on kissFlix.co ]
[In my prime]
[Episode 20]
Dad,
why did you lie to me?
I didn't exactly lie.
I only meant to wait
a bit longer before telling you the truth.
I was afraid you'd be affected
when you knew it.
Cao Xin,
don't feel burdened.
This matter has nothing to do with you.
Look...
Our house was practically
falling apart.
It's a good thing that I sold it early.
Now, I'm living at Si's place
while helping
her take care of her child.
How very nice.
Dad.
I've made up my mind.
I'm not going abroad.
You're not going abroad?
After four years of hard work,
you finally got into grad school.
And now you're giving up on it?
Yes, I am.
I've decided.
Alright, Cao Xin.
It is
really late now.
Let's go home for some rest.
You need to calm down.
Let's go.
Dad.
I didn't say that on impulse
or out of anger.
I've been thinking about this
since the day I got
the admission letter
from Macdonald University.
I want to take charge of my own life
for just once.
Take charge of your own life
for just once?
Does that conflict with your education?
I'd really hate to have you,
Grandpa, and Si
live in misery for the rest of your lives
because of me.
Grandpa is really old now,
yet he has to leave his hometown
because of me.
Doesn't he want
to plant flowers
and bask in the sun
in our hometown?
And look at you, working
as a security guard,
braving the weather and catering
to other people's moods.
Cao Xin, enough.
We are willing
to do all of this.
And we're doing it of our own accord.
I've always been catering
to other people's moods
and I've got used to it
over these many years.
That's why I hoped you could
put your heart
into studies,
go to a great college,
and find a good job,
so you would have a decent life
and never have to cater to anyone.
I wish for you to hold your head high
and walk a path
to prosperity
that I never got to walk.
Cao Xin.
Call me selfish
or narrow-minded if you like.
I just want to do everything I can
to send you out of here.
I want you to make something of yourself.
I want you to achieve success.
Do it for my sake,
will you?
Dad,
what does success mean?
What does it mean
to make something of myself?
In my opinion, what matters is
that our whole family lives
happily together every day.
Only that is the foundation of success.
Cao Xin,
everyone says that a good man's ambition
reaches far and wide.
But look at you...
That's why I envy Qi Shi.
It's true that she didn't go to college,
but in these four years,
she managed to open a clothing store
through her own efforts,
Indeed, it was a rough journey,
but she must have found joy,
because she chose this path herself.
Up till today,
I've never been
happy about getting a scholarship
from Macdonald University,
because I didn't choose any of that.
It was a path that you chose
for me long ago.
Since I was little, I've always
told myself
that I must listen to you,
be a good son,
and do everything you said.
Do you remember
that when Qi Shi was eight
and about to start elementary school,
you took us both
to the stationery store?
Qi Shi asked for a toy.
I was actually
the one who wanted that toy.
I asked Qi Shi to get it for me,
because I dared not to do so myself.
Therefore, now,
I want to take charge of my own life
for just once.
Dad.
Cao Xin,
I understand everything
you're saying.
But sometimes,
it's wrong to be willful.
You should be more considerate of others,
alright?
Fine.
I get it now.
You've grown up
and you have your own ideas.
You don't need me anymore.
Dad.
It's not that I don't need you.
I'm just feeling...
now that I'm gradually growing up
I hope I can become someone
who you can rely on.
Let's go home.
Dad.
Actually, the sweater Mrs. Huo knitted
is quite cozy.
The one you knitted...
is too tight.
You little brat.
Looking down on your old man now?
No,
I'm just stating a fact.
Here, your clothes.
Thirty, right?
Do come back again.
-Thirty yuan for you.
-There are new arrivals every week.
Come again whenever you feel like.
Sure.
You... you...
Come here!
Your business
is really booming.
So busy that you're having lunch
this late.
There have been better times.
Watch out for that plump woman
next door.
It seems she's not to be trifled with.
Especially since you got here,
her business has obviously taken a hit.
I gave out gifts
to
the neighbors when I opened this shop.
Everyone was pretty friendly.
Hua, the owner next door,
even suggested
we look out for each other.
Only this plump lady
sees me as a thorn in her side.
Tell me.
Isn't the key to doing
business lies in one's own skills?
Can hatred
help with anything?
Will it make her business any better?
I don't know if it'll get better.
But ever since you showed up,
her business is clearly
going under.
When people can't get first place,
they blame those who can
for being too good.
Classic Cao the Second thinking.
Cao Xin was going to study abroad,
but he gave up in the end.
He's getting prepared to find a job now.
Even Cao the Second has made progress.
How is that any progress?
He had been always
suppressed
by his dad at home
and by me at school since he was a kid.
He never lived for himself
for a single day.
I believe he must have gone through
a lot of
inner struggle before he made
such a huge decision.
Qi Shi,
you know what?
Actually, you and Cao Xin
can make a pretty good couple.
D-Don't you speak nonsense.
It's been ages since I last saw him.
How are we supposed to make a good couple?
Exactly.
It's been ages since you last saw him.
Why are you
still refusing to meet with him?
I'm not refusing it. I just don't see
any necessity.
How is that
even an excuse? You two are friends.
He has never
stopped caring about you.
Tian Zihao told me that Cao Xin even
sent you a flower basket
when you opened this shop.
I know.
Sometimes,
Cao Xin even texts me.
The more honest
and unbothered he is,
the more ashamed I feel.
I can lose to anyone,
except him.
I just won't accept it.
The truth is,
ever since he got into
Beining University,
he's left me far behind.
He and I are
worlds apart now.
He's not going abroad for studies.
And you have your career now.
How is there
a big gap between the two of you?
Have you heard
of this? "Things change over time."
Cao Xin and I have
already missed
our chance.
Of course,
maybe we're back
to the same starting point now.
And who knows?
Perhaps one day,
our paths might cross again.
Please make way!
Let me through!
Make way.
♪ Who hasn't panicked
in this fast-paced world? ♪
♪ All I see is the look in your eyes ♪
♪ If there's nothing left tomorrow ♪
♪ I'll still walk you home ♪
Here you are, sir.
Didn't we agree on 15?
Round it down.
I'll hire your service again.
Thanks, sir.
Bye. Wish you a booming business.
My phone!
Thank you.
Qi Shi!
Miss,
look at this.
It's a new arrival.
I think it suits you perfectly.
Look, try it against yourself.
A cute camisole.
I think it looks great on you.
This piece will really
flatter your proportions.
See? It reduces...
What kind of garbage did you sell me?
I demand a refund!
Everyone, gather around!
Come take a look!
This shop sells junk!
Don't buy clothes from them!
The clothes
they're selling will kill you!
Come, everyone!
Come take a look!
You tell me who's in the wrong here.
A couple of days ago, my daughter
bought some clothes here.
After wearing them for just a few days,
she broke out
in huge red rashes!
All red and itchy!
I asked an expert,
and guess what?
-What?
-Any findings?
Those are discarded clothes from overseas!
-Discarded clothes from overseas?
-Foreign clothing waste?
I heard such used clothing from overseas
was stripped off dead people.
And
it's covered in
germs and pathogens that cause
infectious diseases.
Exactly!
Aren't these clothes banned
in the market now?
Where did she get this stuff?
Ma'am!
Ma'am.
Come with m.e
Ma'am,
you sell clothes nearby, right?
You are a mother too, aren't you?
Come on,
you be the judge.
Whoever sells clothes like those
has no conscience at all, right?
How can we let this slide?
Don't we deserve justice?
We can't let this slide!
She must be punished!
This is unacceptable!
Enough, enough!
The truth is not out yet.
How can you just conclude
the problem lies in the clothes?
This...
Those clothes are worn next to the skin.
If not the clothes,
where else could the problem be?
-Exactly.
-She has a point.
This shop must be investigated.
I am going to
tear down her shop
today!
I...
Stay away from my shop!
You can't...
Don't touch my stuff!
Stay away from my shop!
There's nothing wrong with my clothes.
How can you do this?
You can't... Don't touch my things!
Let me see.
Her hair's all white.
The shop owner must be sick!
What kind of illness is this?
Her hair's all white at this young age.
Could it be a contagious disease?
Yes, contagious!
Contagious? Hell no.
Don't you have any common sense?
It's not contagious.
I'm her blood sister.
Do I look sick to you?
Listen, everyone, step back.
Make way please.
Hello.
We're market administrators of Wulin Road
Commercial Street.
You said you were scammed
into buying foreign
clothing waste in our market, right?
Then come
with us
to the market administration office.
We'll get to the bottom of this.
I didn't ask for your help.
This is...
only a trivial matter.
You shouldn't be bothered.
A trivial matter?
The noise and disruption
you made in public
have caused damage to this shopping
street...
Si.
And the reputation
of this legally registered
shop named All the Rage.
Regardless,
you must come with us
for a thorough investigation.
There are rules in this market.
Any fellow traders found maliciously
disrupting market order will be expelled
without exception
in serious cases.
Come with us!
Qi Shi.
Hold on!
You said you bought from my shop,
right?
But only these are the clothes in my shop.
I sourced all my goods
through official channels in Shenguang.
I've carefully checked
every piece of clothing
and tagged them all.
I solemnly promise you all here,
that if anyone buys
defective goods
or foreign clothing waste from me,
I'll pay you ten times the price!
So she really was framed.
Alright.
Get a move on. Come with us.
Break it up, everyone.
Break it up.
Off you go.
-Don't gather around.
-Break it up.
Dad told me
you opened a shop here too.
Isn't it a huge coincidence?
My shop is on this street too.
It's right at the end of the street.
Looks like I didn't do enough research.
I shouldn't have been lazy.
At that time, I was just busy
building good relations
with neighboring shops.
I should have walked a bit further down.
That way, I would have
run into you earlier.
Little did I imagine
that we'd end up in the same business.
But a smart girl like you will surely
succeed in everything you do.
If you had continued
your education years ago...
Si,
compliment me all you want,
but just don't bring up the past.
A true hero never dwells on past glories.
You don't blame me?
I could blame anyone but you.
You didn't do anything wrong.
If I am to name one thing
that I've learned out here
over these years...
I'd say the most important one
is to never cling to the past.
We have to look forward.
You see,
our lives are
getting better and better, right?
For all it's worth,
we're two beautiful shop owners
at opposite ends
of this shopping street.
You've really grown up.
Talking to you takes me back
to when were kids,
playing and messing around
in the yard.
Do you remember
when you were little,
you caught caterpillars to scare Cao Xin?
He was so frightened that he
couldn't sleep for days.
He got really bad dark circles
under his eyes.
Are you two still in touch?
No, I've been too busy to talk to him.
Si, did you bring your phone?
Let's exchange numbers
so we can keep in touch.
Breakfast is ready!
Doudou.
How can you play with my phone again?
You should've stopped him.
Hand it over.
Don't play with Mom's phone.
Play with Dad's. Here.
No playing with your phone either.
Time to eat.
Right, let's eat.
I'll go get chopsticks.
I wonder how our son's
job hunt is going.
What's the rush?
Why put so much pressure on him?
Just let him take his time.
We should look on the bright side.
Look,
before, he was completely
out of our sight.
But now, he's back, safe and sound.
So, be content.
Easy for you to say.
Our son used to be
so ambitious
and full of spirit.
He aspired to be a world champion.
Everyone in the neighborhood
praised him, didn't they?
And now look,
he can't even find a job.
Zhi never shows it
because he's considerate.
You know?
Deep down, he must very upset.
Well,
our downstairs neighbor, Li,
has a grandson
who just returned from abroad.
Isn't that young lad
also unemployed right now?
Our son can't find a job
right away, and that's normal.
Neither have we found
a proper business
to do now, right?
Isn't it the same?
We moved all the way
from Qingwu to Haizhou.
W-W-We
have spent so much money,
with no revenue coming in.
I...
I checked out some storefronts
in Haizhou today.
The rent is 10 times
higher than in Qingwu.
That much? That expensive?
How about this?
We'll go back to our old trade.
Let our son run a street stall with me.
Rest assured.
I guarantee he won't starve
as long as I am around.
Oh, cut it out.
You...
actually
take pride in running a street stall?
Are you even looking for
an heir or what?
Why? Anything wrong
with running a street stall?
Son,
you're back.
Yes, Mom, I'm back.
Haven't eaten yet, have you?
I'll go get you food.
No need, Mom. I...
I-I-I
already made
dinner and kept it
here for you.
-Come on.
-Dad.
Sit down and eat.
I bought some fruit.
Okay.
Come on.
I steamed these buns today.
Have a bowl of porridge.
Here.
Pickles.
We waited a long time for you.
Mom, Dad,
if I come back too late again,
don't wait for me.
Just go to sleep.
It's fine.
Your mom and I have
nothing else to do anyway.
Right.
We were just chatting.
Yes.
We chatted as we watched TV.
Well, today I went
to see my former coach
from the sports school.
He left the school the year before last
and then set up
a comprehensive physical
training center for kids.
He told me to try working there tomorrow.
Is he that former coach of yours,
surnamed Ma?
That's
our son's former coach.
He ran around
and helped a lot
when Zhi was in trouble.
Oh, Coach Ma.
T-Then make sure you do a good job.
I got it.
Don't worry.
I know what to do.
Coach Ma, you wanted to see me?
From now on,
you'll be teaching general fitness.
Later on,
go with Yang
to sit in on some classes
so as to learn
how he teaches.
Just relax!
You've mastered
more than enough
to teach some children.
Now,
let us show you around the venue.
Thank you, Coach.
No problem. Just relax.
On your toes. Then step forward.
Here we go.
That's right. Keep going.
Continue.
Good. Now,
let's review the starting position.
One and a half foot lengths
behind the starting line.
Move this foot back a bit.
Alright. Now raise your hips.
What's there to say?
Get ready to run.
Keep your hips up.
Stop it now.
A parent of a child here
is from Qingwu.
She recognized you.
So...
What kind of training school is this?
You hired a teacher who's been to prison!
How can we trust this kind of person
with our child?
Listen to me.
Please hear me out.
Mr. Qi
did run into a bit of trouble years ago.
Nonetheless,
there's absolutely
no problem with his character.
His professional skills
are second to none.
He even won first place
in the Provincial Games back in the day.
I don't care for that!
All I know is
that he's an ex-convict.
Winning first place
in the Provincial Games
or nationals means nothing.
Let me ask you.
Is he an ex-convict or not?
It's just unacceptable
that you assign an ex-convict
to teach our child.
Okay, fine.
How about this?
This training center
would like to make
a gesture of benevolence
by offering you a 10% discount
on this semester's tuition fees.
Who cares about that little discount?
Today, you will have to either
assign a different coach
or give us a refund!
Exactly!
B-B-But...
I'm telling you,
we're quitting.
Training centers like yours
can be seen everywhere.
Yes!
We demand a refund!
-Refund!
-We demand a refund!
Coach.
P-Please listen to me.
I know you've been
helping me all these years.
I can't repay you with much.
But at least
I shouldn't cause you any more trouble.
I-It's fine. I'll talk to them...
Please let me finish.
With how things are today,
I have to leave,
or the parents won't calm down.
Sorry.
And thank you.
My apologies for all this trouble.
I'm sorry.
Let me.
Parents,
I'm sorry.
I'll be leaving right now.
My apologies
for causing such trouble.
Get a move on. Go away!
-Leave already!
-Off you go!
Get lost!
-Leave!
-Seriously.
You always refused to meet with me
when you were behind bars.
Now, you're finally free.
Yet you still wouldn't come see me.
I meant to meet with you,
but I didn't have the guts.
It was my fault
that you didn't get into college.
You should hate me.
Qi Zhi,
you're taking yourself
way too seriously.
With my grades,
do you really think
you could be an obstacle
on my way to college?
I do hate you.
I hate you so much.
I hate you for throwing away
your bright future
in the heat of the moment.
I hate you for not even bothering
to come see me after leaving prison.
Have you
forgotten me, your own sister?
No.
I swear I haven't.
It's true that I didn't get into college.
That's my fate.
But I refuse to accept it.
I've never given in to it.
Look at me now.
I have made it
in Haizhou
all by myself.
What about you?
Have you accepted your fate?
Well, you've admitted defeat.
I never meant to do so.
But you see what's going on now.
Nobody
will hire an ex-con.
The way you behave now truly maddens me.
It's just a job, right?
If one way doesn't work, then try another.
Why do you have to be so sulky?
Does it help?
Ever since I was little,
because of my illness,
I've suffered much
pain and disdain.
But have I ever complained?
I made it through at last, didn't I?
Look at me now.
Aren't I doing just fine?
I'm even doubting if...
if we truly are biological siblings.
How come you're nothing like me at all?
Show some respect.
If anything, you're the one
who's not like me.
The fact is I'm not changing
to another path.
I simply have no paths choose from.
I don't think
your failure to find a job
is largely related to you being
an ex-convict.
We're in adversity
due to lack of education.
I'm just not cut out
for studies.
You know that.
Since I was a kid,
even reading a manual
could make me sleepy.
Yeah, right.
I'm not asking you to take that path.
Only I am the scholar of the family.
I won't force you.
I know.
Whether it was school back then
or work now,
my sister can always hold her own.
I put you through so much misery.
Instead of kowtowing to you,
let me make an apology.
I'm sorry.
You can deliver goods for me.
Deliver goods?
I opened a store
in Haizhou.
I can't manage everything alone.
What now?
Feeling too embarrassed to work
for your own sister?
No. That's not what I mean.
Delivery guys
should know how to drive cars, right?
But I don't.
I'm afraid I'll get in your way.
Then go and learn to drive.
Gosh.
Thank you for your support, Mr. Wang.
-Goodbye.
-Keep up the good work.
Take care.
See Mr. Wang out for me.
This way, Mr. Wang.
Please.
Let's go.
Indeed, young people are
really bold.
I made a right choice
by hiring you as my assistant
out of hundreds of candidates.
How did you come up with
the idea of changing our long-standing
allocation system
to an ordering fair?
I thought it this way:
distributors are on the front line
of the industry.
They are the ones who understand
consumer needs best.
A bottom-up approach
to style selection can
most effectively minimize inventory
and deliver win-win outcomes
to both the brand and distributors.
Well said.
But it's not easy
to implement
a whole new system.
How about this?
In three days,
submit
a feasibility study report to me.
Is there a problem?
I can make it in two days.
Very good. A promising future awaits you.
Keep up the good work.
Oh, right.
My father fell ill.
He needs a substitute teacher
for his English class this week.
Are you interested?
Qi Shi,
be honest with me.
Are you wearing colored contacts or not?
This is the natural color of my eyes.
Jealous?
Such a pretty color of your eyes.
They seem like a foreigner's.
But I have poor eyesight.
Did you take notes last class?
Can I copy them?
Sure.
Great. Thanks.
Look, guys!
What a handsome young man!
He's so cute!
Look!
A handsome man!
I can't see him.
Sir,
did you walk into the wrong classroom?
Our English teacher
is hardly as handsome as you are.
Hello everyone, my name is Cao Xin.
Your English teacher had
a little emergency today.
So I'm subbing for him in this class.
Handsome,
don't just sub for him in one class.
You should take over
all our future classes.
-Yes!
-Go ahead and do it!
Your English teacher is well-connected.
I dare not steal his job.
Now, let's review what you learned
in the previous class.
Can one of you recap it for us?
Qi Shi.
Is Qi Shi not here?
Qi Shi,
the teacher's asking for you.
Please tell me your name.
My name is Qi Shi.
My name is Cao Xin.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you... too.
Can you tell me about yourself?
I'm Qi Shi.
I come from a small village
called Qingwu Town.
I'm 22 years old.
Why do you come here...
to learn Business English?
Because I want to improve myself
and communicate with foreigners,
especially the talented ones.
What's your highest degree?
Sorry.
Next question.
I haven't been to college.
♪ The wind blew through our hair ♪
♪ The story slowly grew complicated ♪
♪ We didn't become anyone's legend ♪
♪ We only learned to grow up in the rain ♪
How have you been?
♪ Are we to blame fate? ♪
♪ Adulthood is bandaging your own fall ♪
I'm good.
♪ Rented rooms, the last bus home ♪
♪ What does the future hold? ♪
No, I'm not.
♪ It's been long since I last had
the guts to say I feared ♪
I had...
really hard times.
♪ Though we have nothing,
we still bustle about ♪
My first job fired me
♪ Because the answer is clear
as long as you are around ♪
because of my education,
and of my...
♪ The old dreams are now covered in dust ♪
♪ But it's okay ♪
my condition.
♪ The morning glow will finally arrive ♪
Then, I was selling clothes in the street,
where I got kicked around here and there,
trying to earn money.
Finally, I...
own
my shop now.
♪ All I see is the look in your eyes ♪
♪ If there's nothing left tomorrow ♪
It's been a long,
♪ I'll still walk you home ♪
long, and difficult time.
But I made it.
Sit down, please.
That's all
for today's class.
See you, if possible.
Sir,
can we have your email address?
This way, we can ask you questions
in the future.
Sir,
do be generous.
Please give us your email address.
Goodbye.
Qi Shi...
I have it—
his email address.
Give me ten yuan and it's yours.
-I want it!
-I want it too!
-Me too!
-Quick!
Count me in!
Fifty yuan for his QQ number.
If you pay me a hundred,
I'll tell you
his phone number too.
Okay.
-I'll pay!
-I'll take that bundle!
-Me first!
-No, me!
I want both numbers.
But not right now.
You have to pay up first.
Let me mark down your names now.
-Put my name down first!
-Mine first!